Hoosier State Press Association mss. 1969-1984 LMC 2717
Lilly Library
- Miscellaneous Files, 1964-1980; 1975 (Box 23)
  - SB46 as Introduced, SB88 as Reported From Senate Judiciary Comm., 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - SB88. Form in Which Passed in Senate Feb. 5, 1975. (Box 24)
  - SB88. Amendments Proposed in House Policy Comm. March 19, 1975. (Box 24)
  - SB88. As Amended March 19, 1975 by House Public Policy Comm. (Box 24)
  - HB1492. Amendments Proposed in Senate Judiciary Comm., 1975 (Box 24)
  - HB1492. As Reported Out of Senate Judiciary Comm. March 18, 1975. (Box 24)
  - HB1492. Amendments Proposed in Senate Subcomm., [1975] (Box 24)
  - HB1492. As Introduced and Amended in House., 1975 (Box 24)
  - SB88, HB1492. Legal Brief "Variable Obscenity for Minors" as Related to Legislation., [1975] (Box 24)
  - HB1510 Civil Proceedings., Undated (Box 24)
  - SB106 1974 Conference Committee Report. (Box 24)